What
have you done, Hammond?
There it is.
Is it Ford Mustang, the Mach one.
It's brilliant.
Unnecessary.
That's the whole point of it.
It's stripped down.
Everything on it is functional.
Is it?
Yes.
This rear spoiler, what does it do?
Nothing.
Racing fuel filler cap?
No.
It's just a cover.
Is the engine 19 feet long?
Well, because they decided they wanted to make the Mustang bigger in '71, and they did that by just making it bigger.
This is all just pointless.
No.
It's bigger.
If I were nine, it would be tremendous, but I'm not.
Should we just turn our attention now to the elephant that isn't in the room?
Had to be a V eight, so I thought it could be a Mercedes.
In fact, we couldn't have been more wrong.
No way.
That is not him.
Not serious.
He's gone completely mad.
Oh, but he thinks he's blonde.
He does think he's blonde.
Gentlemen, the Lotus Esprit twin turbo V eight.
But Lotus does not have a good reputation for quality.
Some say that this stands for lots of trouble, usually serious.